that call by me.
>> You called two timeouts. Were you
considering different calls or
>> thought about maybe trying to draw them
off sides? I took one, they took the
other. And um it was a uh poor decision
by me right there. But um you know, you
give the Niners credit, they made enough
plays to be able to win the football
game. We had plenty of chances
throughout this game. You know, we
stayed in it. We fought, we battled. Um,
but there's a lot of things that we have
to be able to clean up and um, a lot of
football left, but uh, I'm pretty sick
right now. I'm sick of the spot that I
put our group in um, to end the game,
but um, hey, these are the tough beats
that you got to be able to learn from
and move forward, and that's what we're
going to do.
>> Any thought of kicking the field goal
there?
>> No.
>> No. In hindsight, I wish I would have,
but uh, no, we we came in here to try to
win the football game. It didn't go down
for us, Gary. That was that wasn't even
a thought. But uh the play selection was
very poor. I'm sick right now because uh
I put our players in a shitty spot and
uh I got to live with that.
>> There were mistakes in all three game
today.
>> Yeah, you have to, you know, ultimately
it's my responsibility. We weren't ready
to go. Um you know, there was a lot of
guys that gave us chances. Um you know,
but I'm really disappointed. Um while
also excited about being able to use
this as an opportunity to be able to
respond. Right now it doesn't feel good.
Um, you know, you were hoping to be able
to have a few days off to be able to
enjoy it and, uh, this will certainly
not make for a great weekend. Uh, but it
will offer an opportunity for us to
continue to show that we're made of the
right stuff, which I have zero doubt. I
do think our execution can be much
sharper in all three phases, and that'll
be a focal point for us when we come
back.
>> Couple more.
>> Sean, when a team has a fourth and
short, you know, why why do you blame
yourself for that particular call? I
mean, obviously didn't work, but
>> I there's there's better, you know, my
job is to try to put our players in
successful situations and outcomes. Um,
and that wasn't it right there.
>> Sean, do unforced errors compound
sometimes for a team. So, did that
happen tonight?
>> Yeah, it did. It did happen. You know,
and I mean, we had a chance to close the
game out and um and ultimately it didn't
go down for us. There was a significant
amount of things, you know, for us to
even be in it, you know, is a real
credit to the resilience of the group,
Jordan. Um, you know, but you're that's
not winning football tonight. You know,
there was a lot of really good plays at
different points that kept us
competitive, gives us a chance to go
into overtime. Um, but we certainly did
more to lose that game than we did win
it tonight. And, um, you know, it did
compound for sure.
>> I'll have to look at the tape. All
right. Thank you guys.
What did you guys see? Sean said some uh
harsh things about himself about the
play call specifically on that fourth
and one. What did you see them doing
that maybe what did you guys see them
doing that maybe led to that call? Uh, I
mean, that's a bread and butter short
yardage call for us. So, I didn't have
any problem with it. That's trusting our
guys to go out there and make a play.
Um, they did a nice job of stopping it.
Um, frustrating that we didn't get it.
Um, wish I would have done more. Um, and
found a way to help us win.
>> I just got to learn from them. Um, you
know, football is an imperfect game.
You're not going to have a perfect game.
I mean, everybody's going to have
mistakes in every single phase, every
week probably. Um, got to minimize those
and make sure that they're not, you
know, uh, you know, as as tough on us as
they were tonight. Um, we battled our
ass off. Um, I don't know how many, you
know, we just kept finding a way to hold
him to a field goal, drive down. Um, you
know, get it punched out, defense, hell
of a job, find a way to get it back
down, field goal makes it, um, you know,
sends it to overtime, find a way to get
a stop, drive it back down. Um, I love
that we went for it. That's what I mean,
we're not playing for a tie. Let's go.
Um, just wish we did, you know, kept the
drive alive and found a way to score.
>> Matthew, can you talk to me about the
energy level from the first half to the
second half that you saw from from the
team?
>> I thought the energy level was fine. Um,
the whole game, you know, we had six
plays or something in the first quarter.
Um, you know, then the next drive we
moved it, you know, right down the
field, had the unfortunate turnover, and
then next drive went down and scored the
ball again. and and that's the way the
game goes sometimes, you know, that's
the way it is. Um they did a nice job of
keeping it in play, converting on third
downs and um we knew it was going to be
just one of those games. Had to wait our
time out a little bit. We did and and uh
got more got more cracks at it um in the
second half and and did a lot with it.
Um just got to find a way to uh not turn
it over as much um you know in crucial
spots and then um you know there at the
end find a way to get another yard.
>> Matt, do you feel like these two losses
are you guys beating yourselves? Can the
posit that it's happening early enough
that you can use like a learning
experience.
>> Football games are like I said earlier,
they're imperfect. Um, we had a chance
to to win it multiple multiple multiple
times. Didn't get it done. Those sting
and piss you off. Um,
uh, you know, I' I'd love for us to find
a way to close a little bit better and I
think we will. Um, you know, but yeah,
that that one's that one's frustrating.
The Philly one's frustrating, but
listen, all we can do is look forward to
the next one and get ready to go.
We can see and hear temperatures are
understandably high after one like this.
How do you keep guys together? Keep this
from
>> Oh, I'm not worried about guys being not
together. Guys are pissed off because
they care. If everybody was laughing and
joking, I'd be a little bit more
concerned. So, um, you know, I feel like
we, you know, had opportunities to win
the game. Like I said multiple times. We
didn't get it done. Guys are ticked. I
like that.
>> What are the pros and cons?
Not many pros. Um, cons are it's a
longer weekend than it would have been.
Thanks,